After a thousand DMs asking the same
question, I figured I'd just make a
video about it. Everybody wants to know
why I'm not in Costa Rica. What am I
doing back in the States? And the answer
is this, life, man. [music]
You got to remember, content creators
are people, too. I am just like you. I'm
a regular old guy who's just been out
there chasing his dreams, but when I
have things that I need to fix, I come
back and handle them cuz that's what a
man does. And I got cars that break
down. I got tenants that tear up my
houses. I have business and family
obligations that I need to take care of.
And if it meant leaving my off-grid
paradise over there, so be it. Because
[music] that's what a man does. He owns
up to his responsibilities and his
obligations before he chases his dreams.
And that's what I'm here doing. The good
news is, after I get done with all this
stuff, [music] we should be able to open
up for our first solar classes, our
first off-grid living experiences, and
some badass Costa Rica travel packages.
[music]
So, if you're in the States and you'd
like to see me, I'll be here for a
little while. I've been offered a chance
to go work on a house in Alaska.
>> [music]
>> Uh I got a solar install in Tennessee.
And other than that, I'm running around
Augusta picking off service calls and
fixing my own houses just like old
times. Just remember, what you seen
[music] me doing, you can do, too. But,
you've got to handle your obligations
before you chase your dreams. And that's
what I'm here doing, guys. I've always
[music] kept it real with you, and I'm
keeping it real with you right now,
sitting on this stump in the park
instead of in the jungle of Costa Rica.
I can't wait to get back, and I cannot
wait to welcome all you there. My name
is Joe Fells, Real Life Dude on the
internet, and I can't wait [music] to
see you in Pura Vida.